<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chattanooga Democratic Socialists of America</title>
    <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chattanooga Democratic Socialists of America</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 17:49:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chattanoogadsa.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Faust Speaks On Medicare For All</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/tim-faust-mfa-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 17:49:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/tim-faust-mfa-talk/</guid>
      <description>Tim Faust, from the DSA National Medicare For All Campaign Committee, is going to be visiting Chattanooga to talk about the necessity of a single payer system and how DSA is planning to campaign for it!
The format will be a thirty minute speech, then a thirty minute Q&amp;amp;A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Quarterly General Meeting 2018</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/general-meeting-q1-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 17:32:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/general-meeting-q1-2018/</guid>
      <description>Poor People&amp;rsquo;s Campaign Beth Foster, co-director of the Mercy Junction Justice and Peace Center, will come and present on the Poor People&amp;rsquo;s Campaign.
The Poor People’s Campaign: A National Call for Moral Revival is uniting tens of thousands of people across the country to challenge the evils of systemic racism, poverty, the war economy, ecological devastation and the nation’s distorted morality. We need you to step up and join our efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking Cooperatives 2017</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/talking-cooperatives-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 01:25:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/talking-cooperatives-2017/</guid>
      <description> Description </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December OC Meeting</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/december-oc-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 01:24:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/december-oc-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Come get organized! Currently, the organizing committee is the life of Chattanooga DSA. Decisions are made at the organizing committee, and plans are presented at organizing committee meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee State Democrats Join Single Payer Fight</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/posts/tndp-joins-single-payer-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 16:28:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/posts/tndp-joins-single-payer-fight/</guid>
      <description>Nov 20, 2017
Dear Editor,
The Chattanooga Democratic Socialists of America welcomes the Tennessee Democratic Party to the struggle for Medicare For All that the grassroots have been pursuing for years now. We hope they bring the humility to follow the work of those fighting for MFA on the ground, the resources to support them, and the exposure their organization can bring to these efforts.
DSA has resolved to make the campaign for Medicare For All a national priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socialist Sunday: Winter Social</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/2017-winter-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 16:29:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/2017-winter-social/</guid>
      <description>Help us organize a year-end party and ring in one whole year of democratic socialism in Chattanooga.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socialism! Anarchism! Communism! Socialist Sundays</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/socialism-anarchism-communism-socialist-sundays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 16:29:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/socialism-anarchism-communism-socialist-sundays/</guid>
      <description>The left is full of jargon and political theory. We&amp;rsquo;ll break it down and explain it bit by bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Reconstruction America</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/reading-reconstruction-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 16:29:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/reading-reconstruction-america/</guid>
      <description>For this discussion we’re going to be reading The Wars of Reconstruction, by Douglas R. Egerton</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2017 General Meeting</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/october-general-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 21:12:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/october-general-meeting/</guid>
      <description>This meeting we&amp;rsquo;re going to be talking about
 Socialist Sundays Disability Awareness Medicare For All  and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September Socialist Sunday Taillight Clinic</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/september-socialist-sunday-taillight-clinic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 20:42:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/events/september-socialist-sunday-taillight-clinic/</guid>
      <description>Description Following the example set by New Orleans DSA, we decided to put on a taillight clinic and serve the people of Chattanooga by replacing taillights for free. We&amp;rsquo;ll be out there for a few hours starting at 2pm.
Tell everyone you know!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join DSA</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 18:54:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/join/</guid>
      <description>National DSA DSA is a member-funded organization with national dues. Dues ensure that DSA remains independent.
 Join DSA   Chattanooga DSA Get involved with Chattanooga DSA by coming to one of our events, joining our mailing list, or getting in touch!
You can also donate directly to Chattanooga DSA and support our efforts.
To be a voting member of Chattanooga DSA, we ask that you join national DSA with link above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>https://chattanoogadsa.org/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 18:54:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chattanoogadsa.org/donate/</guid>
      <description>Donate to Chattanooga DSA  In analyzing the situation here in Chattanooga, TN, we have found that there is a lack of institutional power that is answerable to the broader population, and most power is wrapped up in and around a few groups of wealthy people.
To build up people power, Chattanooga DSA has decided to focus on mutual aid actions aiming to find a place where we can build community power parallel to the current power structure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>